<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Home Screen</string>
    <string name="navigation_open">Open Navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_close">Close Navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="title_activity_terms">ScrollingActivity</string>
    <string name="large_text">
        The KnowToGrow service is made available for personal, non-commercial use only.
        Broadcasting the same through any means, including but not limited to through
        the internet, television, handheld devices and other devices, is not permitted
        and will be considered as a breach of Intellectual Property Rights of the Company.
        The reserves the rights to terminate the subscription without any prior notice and
        also to initiate any legal proceedings in case of such breach. Business, organizations
        or other legal entities are strictly debarred from using the KnowToGrow services for any purpose.\n\n
        The user is prohibited from using the KnowToGrow service for any illegal or unauthorized purpose.
        International users agree to comply with all local rules regarding online conduct and acceptable
        content, including laws regulating the export of data from India. The user is solely responsible
        for his conduct and any data, text, information, graphics, photos, profiles, audio and video clips,
        links and other material that he submits, posts and displays on the KnowToGrow service.\n\n
        KnowToGrow accepts no responsibility for the material and contents, accuracy, conformity to applicable laws of such material.\n\n
        In the preparation of the Application/Website/Services/products and contents therein, every effort has been made to offer the most
        current, correct, and clearly expressed information possible. Nevertheless, inadvertent errors may occur. In particular, but without
        limiting anything here, the Company disclaims any responsibility for any errors and accuracy of the information that may be contained
        in the Application. Any feedback from User is most welcome to make the Application and contents thereof error free and user friendly.
        Company also reserves the right and discretion to make any changes/corrections or withdraw/add contents at any time without notice.
        Neither the Company nor any third parties provide any warranty or guarantee as to the accuracy, timeliness, performance, completeness
        or suitability of the information and materials found or offered on Application/Website/Services/products for any particular purpose.
        You acknowledge that such information and materials may contain inaccuracies or errors and we expressly exclude liability for any such
        inaccuracies or errors to the fullest extent permitted by law.\n\n
        Certain contents in the Application/Services/Website/products (in particular relating to assistance in preparations for administrative services)
        may contain opinions and views. The Company shall not be responsible for such opinions or any claims resulting from them. Further, the Company
        makes no warranties or representations whatsoever regarding the quality, content, completeness, or adequacy of such information and data.

    </string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
</resources>
