<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Navigation Try</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Android Studio</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">android.studio@android.com</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="menu_home">Home</string>
    <string name="menu_gallery">Gallery</string>
    <string name="menu_slideshow">Slideshow</string>
    <string name="title_activity_terms">Terms and Conditions</string>
    <string name="large_text">
        The KnowToGrow service is made available for personal, non-commercial use only.
        Broadcasting the same through any means, including but not limited to through
        the internet, television, handheld devices and other devices, is not permitted
        and will be considered as a breach of Intellectual Property Rights of the Company.
        The reserves the rights to terminate the subscription without any prior notice and
        also to initiate any legal proceedings in case of such breach. Business, organizations
        or other legal entities are strictly debarred from using the KnowToGrow services for any purpose.\n\n
        The user is prohibited from using the KnowToGrow service for any illegal or unauthorized purpose.
        International users agree to comply with all local rules regarding online conduct and acceptable
        content, including laws regulating the export of data from India. The user is solely responsible
        for his conduct and any data, text, information, graphics, photos, profiles, audio and video clips,
        links and other material that he submits, posts and displays on the KnowToGrow service.\n\n
        KnowToGrow accepts no responsibility for the material and contents, accuracy, conformity to applicable laws of such material.\n\n
        In the preparation of the Application/Website/Services/products and contents therein, every effort has been made to offer the most
        current, correct, and clearly expressed information possible. Nevertheless, inadvertent errors may occur. In particular, but without
        limiting anything here, the Company disclaims any responsibility for any errors and accuracy of the information that may be contained
        in the Application. Any feedback from User is most welcome to make the Application and contents thereof error free and user friendly.
        Company also reserves the right and discretion to make any changes/corrections or withdraw/add contents at any time without notice.
        Neither the Company nor any third parties provide any warranty or guarantee as to the accuracy, timeliness, performance, completeness
        or suitability of the information and materials found or offered on Application/Website/Services/products for any particular purpose.
        You acknowledge that such information and materials may contain inaccuracies or errors and we expressly exclude liability for any such
        inaccuracies or errors to the fullest extent permitted by law.\n\n
        Certain contents in the Application/Services/Website/products (in particular relating to assistance in preparations for administrative services)
        may contain opinions and views. The Company shall not be responsible for such opinions or any claims resulting from them. Further, the Company
        makes no warranties or representations whatsoever regarding the quality, content, completeness, or adequacy of such information and data.

    </string>
    
    <string name="FAQ">

<b> "Q: Do you provide college admission/ job recruitment
        assistance?</b> \n"
        "No."

<b> "Q:	Are your Counsellors professionally skilled?</b> \n"
       "All our counsellors are professionally skilled. Many are"
       "from the psychology background having sound"
       "experience in counselling and psychometric. Others"
       "are also having ample experience in counselling and"
       "education guidance with the myriad of experience that"
       "they have from their established careers."

<b>"Q: After assessment, will your app get me a job also? </b>\n"
      "No, we strictly do not promote any admission or job"
      "recruitment."

<b>"Q: Do you also have any assessment for especially abled
      students?</b>\n"
      "No, not currently.\n"
<b>"Q: Can students with visual/hearing impairment also sit for
      this aptitude test?</b>\n"
      "If the impairment does not interfere with normal"
      "functioning and the applicant is leading a normal life"
      "going to a normal school, it may be sure taken up."

<b>"Q: Is the aptitude test available in other languages also?</b>\n"
      "No, not as of now but we surely intend to enter that"
      "zone very soon."

<b>"Q: With all the career assessments out there, why should I
       choose your aptitude test?</b>\n"
      "Although there are many assessments, few, if any,"
      "approached work from a comprehensive perspective."
      "Fewer still covered all four aspects of career selection"
      "(Personality, Interests, Skills, and Study Habits). Most"
      "only cover one or two of these areas. More than one of"
      "test is usually necessary to cover all of the components"
      "a complete personal profile. Our aptitude test was"
      "developed based on comprehensive principles and"
      "designed to provide a full profile in one assessment"
      "report."

<b>"Q: What makes KnowToGrow unique?</b>\n"
      "Components of our KnowToGrow app provide"
      "information which is inspired from the recently proposed"
      "education system also the aptitude test is designed"
      "accordingly as all the subjects from different streams"
      "are added to it for a better understanding of students."

<b>"Q: What is Career Assessment?</b>\n"
      "An assessment is a series of questions or statements"
      "that one answers or responds to, that are then scored"
      "by hand or computer. The results are provided in a report"
      "that measures or gives feedback on the particular topic"
      "(aptitude, personality, interest, adjustment, etc.) of the"
      "assessment. A Career Assessment gives information"
      "about careers and helps one make wise career-related"
      "decisions."

<b>"Q: Why is Career planning and guidance Important?
     Does Career Guidance make a difference?</b>\n"
      "Your career is totally your responsibility. Career planning"
      "and guidance helps one to develop a set of career goals,"
      "strategy and options based on your aptitude, interests,"
      "personality, values and skills. Once you have a plan, you"
      "will be equipped to self-manage your career and take"
      "advantage of changes in the economy and job market"
      "rather than becoming a victim of change. Your career"
      "decisions will dramatically impact your lifestyle. Your"
      "occupation will determine where you live, your income,"
      "your work hours, your travels, job security, your choice"
      "of work associates and friends, and how you spend your"
      "leisure time."

<b>"Q: What is the accuracy of suggested careers in the app?</b>\n"
      "The accuracy would depend on how seriously or honestly"
      "the Career Aptitude Test is taken, since the interpretation"
      "and suggested careers would completely depend on the"
      "Test results. Moreover, the suggested careers are"
      "optimised suggestions of your Interest, Personality"
      "and Aptitude."

<b>"Q: What is the assurance of the legitimacy of the
       shortlisted careers?</b>\n"
      "There are many ways to find out the right career like"
      "suggestions from Friends, Family, Teachers,Coaching"
      "Institutes, Jyotish, etc. Our methodology of choosing"
      "the right career is psychometric tests based on"
      "cognitive science."
      "It is one of the most proven and accepted methods"
      "across the globe. Our reliability and validity report"
      "of sample students indicates the consistency and"
      "accuracy. Although no one can be 100% sure about"
      "the right career, but this method is one of the best"
      "methodologies in career counselling."

<b>"Q: What if a student has something in mind, but want to
     explore other options as well?</b>\n"
      "The test results are unbiased, so you can explore"
      "careers based on the suggested career options."

<b>"Q: What is the difference between paper-based test in
    career counselling centres and your approach?</b>\n"
     "Our approach is online test and automated report"
     "with an algorithm calculating a combination of more"
     "than 1000 careers, which manually is very difficult"
     "to achieve. The chances of errors in making answers,"
     "incorporating thousands of factors and shortlisting"
     "careers in report is negligible in automated report"
     "compared to paper-based tests. Moreover, the online"
     "test and automated report is far more cost effective"
     "and less time consuming with much better results."
    </string>
    
</resources>